Contact

sthunga@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/sara-thungabs-rn-5080bb170 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Volunteering Hospitals

Certifications

Mental Health First Aid Registered Nurse Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Sara Thunga, BS, RN

New Graduate Registered Nurse Seeking Employment New York

Summary

I am a highly energetic and organized new graduate Registered Nurse from New York University. I have experience in critical care through a nurse externship on a Step-Down unit at Hospital for Special Surgery and ICU shadowing at NYU Langone Tisch. I worked as a Patient Care Assistant at the Hospital for Special Surgery during my last year of nursing school. In addition, I have perioperative experience from working at a Surgery Center throughout college. I am passionate about volunteer work, as I have been on several medical mission trips to Montana, the Dominican Republic, and Honduras. My most enjoyable clinical rotation was pediatrics, and I have relevant experience with this patient population through nannying and working as a student teacher at my dance studio.

Although I am open to field of nursing, I have developed an interest in critical care and pediatric nursing from my clinical experiences. Please feel free to contact me at: sthunga@comcast.net for any further information.

Experience

Hospital for Special Surgery Patient Care Assistant September 2019 - March 2020 (7 months)

Greater New York City Area

Duties include: helping patients wash up and ambulate, changing linens, preparing rooms for incoming patients, obtaining vital signs and discharging patients.

Hospital for Special Surgery Nurse Extern June 2019 - July 2019 (2 months) Greater New York City Area

Worked as a nurse extern as part of the Hospital for Special Surgery's 8-week externship program. Worked night shifts directly under a nurse preceptor on the hospital's step-down unit. Gained experience working in a more critical care setting by caring for patients experiencing surgical complications.

Advocate Condell Medical Center Intern June 2017 - January 2019 (1 year 8 months) Greater Chicago Area

Worked as an intern at a new Surgicenter. Duties included: helping close the operating rooms after surgery, aiding nurses in recovering patients post-surgery and readying patients before surgery, and cleaning up used equipment and beds.

Education

New York University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2016 - 2020)